CONTACT



lianaelindgren@gmail.com



651-343-8296



liana-morrison111



LianaSun

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARTS: DIETETICS

2004

College of St. Benedict, St. Joseph, MN

MASTERS OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION: ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT

MANAGEMEN 2017

Cyd-Cor, Applied MBA

SOCIAL MEDIA MARKETING CERTIFICATE

2017

eMarketing Insitute

1000 HR YOGA TEACHER CERTIFICATE

2007

Yoga College of India

FULL-STACK ENGINEERING

2019 - July 11th, 2019

University of Minnesota,

College of Cont. Education &

Professional Studies

CORE COMPETENCIES

Leadership

Team management

Relationship building/customer service

Results-Driven

Problem solving

Critical Thinking

Adaptability & flexibility

Project, Process & Team

Management

Strategy & Negotiation

Advanced proficiency in Google

Apps

Strong Communicator

Engaged learner

Technically savvy

Web Development & Design

Graphic & Logo Design

LIANA MORRISON

ABOUT

Liana is a Full-Stack Developer & MBA focused on attention to detail, working collaboratively with team members and contributing to the overall success of the team. Technical skills include HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript/jQuery, Node, Express, MongoDB & MySQL. Tools used are GitHub, Slack methodology, in addition to being an accomplished Project Manager, Senior Sales Associate, Business Manager and Event Planner with over 12 years experiences.

EXPERIENCE

SALES CONSULTANT

First Choice Coffee Services | 2017-2018

First Choice Coffee Services offers premium office coffee and beverages solutions, the latest, upscale and environmentally friendly options for businesses employees and their clients

Client Acquisition thru face to face contact/Territory management

Proposal and cost-analysis writing

Client relationship building and maintenance

Manage and prioritize daily activities and long-term projects

Left to pursue Full-Stack Engineering

SENIOR ACCOUNT MANAGER

Mercury Matrix, Inc | Jan 2017 - Sept 2017

Client Acquisition thru face to face contact/Territory management

Proposal and cost-analysis writing

Client relationship building and maintenance

Manage and prioritize daily activities and long-term projects

Hired, train and coach new team members

Developed strategies to increase brand exposure and revenues

Responsible to meet daily and weekly sales goals

Analyze weekly results and strategize activities to meet goals

Left due to company closing.

SENIOR TEACHER AND STUDIO MANAGER

Open Minds Fusion Studio|Yoga College of India | Nov 2007 - Present

Taught yoga classes and led workshops to increase body awareness and energetic alignment

Participate in research projects with veterans and PTSD using yoga as part of therapy towards recovery.

Design and lead workshops focusing on yoga's health benefits and categories of poses

Manage a private clientele to meet their specific needs and modify training to ensure safety during training

Maintain digital database of clients

Manage day-to-day activities of the office

Create and campaign special events, workshops and parties

Manage a staff of 20-30 contractors

Schedule outside rentals

Develop and implemented training's and other workshops

Head of Mentorship Training Program for new teachers

Co-Creator and Senior Teacher of Earth Goddess Yoga